couponsense.com 2014-10-22

# Coupon Sense Privacy Policy | Coupon Sense - Using Coupons Makes Sense!

**Agreement between user and Coupon Sense Inc.**

The use of this website http://www.CouponSense.com (Coupon Sense Inc.) is offered to you, the user, conditioned on your acceptance without modification of this Terms of Use Agreement. Your use of this website constitutes your agreement to these Terms of Use. If you do not accept these terms and conditions, please do not use our website services. If you have any questions, please contact us. We may amend this Agreement at any time by posting such amendment on the Coupon Sense Inc. website.

**No unlawful or prohibited use**

As a condition of your use of this website, you represent and warrant to Coupon Sense Inc. that you will not use this website for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms of Use. Coupon Sense Inc. promotes only the legal and ethical use of coupons. Continued use of this website is contingent upon of your adherence to this policy. Coupon Sense Inc. is not responsible for the improper use of coupons by Coupon Sense Inc. members. Members who violate this policy may be permanently banned from the Coupon Sense web site.

**Personal and noncommercial use limitation**

Coupon Sense Inc. is for your personal and noncommercial use. You may not copy, modify, distribute, display, perform, create derivative works from, transfer or sell any information, software, products or services obtained from Coupon Sense Inc.

**Email Contact**

Coupon Sense Inc. views the ability to communicate via email as an essential form of contact with our customers and an important part of our savings service. By giving us your email address, you agree to allow Coupon Sense Inc. to send you information and promotional information from time to time. Where multiple email lists are available, participation in the alternative lists is completely optional and voluntary. However, certain Coupon Sense Inc. membership announcements will be sent to all available member email addresses. Ensuring that we have your current email address on file is your responsibility. If you do not want any email in any form, use our online preferences (where available) or call our customer service department to have your email address removed entirely from our database. Coupon Sense Inc. does not and will not sell, rent or lease email addresses to third parties for promotional use. We do send along exceptional offers from third parties to our members, but only when we judge that the nature of the offer represents a significant value to our members.

**Cancellations and Refunds**

Please allow three business days to cancel your account if your request is made online. You can find the Cancel My Account button inside the My Account Tab. If you call our number, 480-883-9012 please allow a week for your cancellation to be processed. You will receive a confirmation email when we have processed your cancellation. We only offer refunds during the trial period.

**Use guidelines and disclaimer**

The Coupon Sense Inc. website serves only as a venue for retail sales and promotion information. The site does not complete the actual transactions between consumers and merchants. The quality, security and legitimacy of the promotions advertised on this site are the solitary responsibility of the retailers offering them, and not within the control of Coupon Sense Inc. Coupon Sense Inc. does not make guarantees for the promotions and prices or any other information posted on this site. This information is published to consumers for free and in good faith. Coupon Sense Inc. will not guarantee the accurateness of any of the advertisements or information published on the site, disseminated through the site, linked to the site, or accessed from the site. Coupon Sense Inc. does not guarantee the value or price of products advertised on our site. In addition Coupon Sense Inc. does not guarantee the quality of services and materials displayed. Coupon Sense Inc. does not guarantee the value of services and materials advertised on sale and obtained by you as a result of using the site’s services. Under no circumstances will Coupon Sense Inc. have any liability for nor consider any claims for:

  * Any loss or damage caused by your reliance on information obtained through the site or
  * Any offer misrepresented or not fulfilled by a merchant/or
  * Any limitations of service due to malfunctions of equipment, lines or service providers beyond its control or due to your failure to fully participate in the service.
  * For any amount in excess of the fees paid by you either individually or in aggregate
  * For any direct, indirect, incidental, punitive or consequential damages of any kind whatsoever with respect to the properties, content and products and services accessible via the same.

Assessing the accuracy and/or usefulness of any offer, promotion or other information available through the site is the sole responsibility of the user. This site, including but not limited to the products, services, and materials described in the site, is provided on an “as is”, “as available” basis. There are no warranties, either expressed or implied, including without limitation, accuracy, availability warranty of merchantability, appropriateness for particular intent and non-infringement. Under no circumstance will Coupon Sense Inc. be liable with regard to this site, including and not limited to the content, product and services described in the site.

Coupon Sense Inc. reserves the right to modify the site, materials, products or services at any time without notice. Some states do not allow the exclusion or limitation of incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitations and exclusions may not apply to you.

**Links to third party sites**

The Coupon Sense Inc. website may contain links to other websites (“linked sites”). These linked sites are not under the control of Coupon Sense Inc. and CouponSense.com is not responsible for the contents of any linked site, including without limitation any link contained in a linked site, or any changes or updates to a linked site. Coupon Sense Inc. is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Coupon Sense Inc. of the site or any association with its operators. Please use your discretion and common sense in accessing any site on the Internet.

**Use of The Message Boards**

The Coupon Sense Inc. site may contain chat rooms, bulletin boards, and message and communication facilities; collectively called “Boards”. You agree to use the Boards only to send and receive messages and information appropriate to the particular Forum. By way of explanation but not limited to, you agree that when using this forum, you will not:

  * Slander, harass, stalk, abuse, threaten or in any way violate such legal rights as privacy and publicity of others.
  * Announce, distribute, broadcast, or publish any slanderous, infringing, obscene, offensive, vulgar or unlawful information or material.
  * Upload files, software or materials protected by intellectual property laws, including copyright or trademarks, without express authorization from the rights holder. Or remove these legal notices or labels or falsify the origin or source of software in any uploaded file.
  * Upload files with viruses or any software programs that may damage another’s computer.
  * With the exception of where expressly allowed, advertise, offer to buy goods or services, conduct surveys, contests or chain letters.
  * Download files posted by another that cannot be legally distributed in this manner. In addition, you acknowledge that these Boards are not endorsed by Coupon Sense Inc., and such communications are not approved by CouponSense.com nor its owner, Coupon Sense Inc. 

Coupon Sense Inc. reserves the right to remove any content in the Boards. Coupon Sense Inc. reserves the right to deny any user access to these Boards without notice.  The Adminstrators and Moderators of the Coupon Sense Community will attempt to keep all objectionable messages off this forum, it is impossible for us to review all messages.  All messages express the views of the author and the owners of Coupon Sense will not be held responsible for the content of any message. By agreeing to these rules, you warrant that you will not post any messages that are obscene, vulgar, sexually-oriented, hateful, threatening, or that violate any laws. The owners and representatives of Coupon Sense reserve the right to remove, edit, move or close any thread for any reason.

**Ownership**

All content on CouponSense.com (including, without limitation, the content, which includes all text, graphics, logos, design features, look and feel, source code, service marks, trademarks, copyrights and other intellectual property, images, processes and software used) is the property of Coupon Sense Inc. or properly licensed by Coupon Sense Inc. from third-party providers and is protected by applicable state, federal and international copyright and other property laws. The compilations on the site (i.e., the collection, arrangement and assembly of all content) are the exclusive property of Coupon Sense Inc. and protected by state, federal and international copyright laws. Users may not make use of any Marks without the expressly written permission of Coupon Sense Inc. All content on the site is protected by copyright. Users of the site are prohibited from modifying or using any of the content of the site for commercial or public purposes. The prohibition includes: modifying, replicating, dispensing, displaying, publishing, selling, trading, licensing, creating derivative works, or presenting the material in any way for personal or commercial usage. Any such unauthorized use will be considered an infringement of Coupon Sense Inc. and/or its suppliers’ and sponsors’ rights or the rights of other parties.

**Changes**

Coupon Sense Inc. reserves the right to modify information on the site or to the service at any time by changing this Agreement. This includes the right to change rules of use, terminate your use and discontinue the service. Coupon Sense Inc. does not guarantee continuous or secure access to our services. Coupon Sense Inc. site operation may be interfered with by several factors outside of our control.

**Laws and regulation**

This Agreement shall be governed in all respects by the laws of the State of Arizona without regard to the conflicts of laws or provisions thereof. By your use of Coupon Sense Inc. and your acceptance of this Agreement and Disclaimer, you agree that any cause of action arising hereunder or otherwise in connection with the site shall be brought forward exclusively and solely in a court in Maricopa County, Arizona. If any provision of this Agreement shall be held by a court of competent jurisdiction to be illegal, invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be limited or eliminated only to the extent necessary to remove such illegality, invalidity or unenforceability, and the unaffected provisions of this Agreement and Disclaimer shall otherwise remain in full force and effect. If any law or regulation of your jurisdiction, or any of your contractual or other obligations or duties would prohibit or restrict you from using all or any part of the site, then you agree to comply therewith and to be the party responsible for any violations thereof, and this Agreement and Disclaimer shall operate to give you notice that Coupon Sense Inc. shall not operate in conflict with any such law, regulation, obligation or duty and does not and will not agree or cooperate knowingly with your use of the site in infringement thereof.

**CouponSense.com copyright**

All content on CouponSense.com (including, without limitation, the content, which includes all text, graphics, logos, design features, look and feel, source code, service marks, trademarks, copyrights and other intellectual property, images, processes and software used) is the property of Coupon Sense Inc. or properly licensed by Coupon Sense Inc. from third-party providers and is protected by applicable state, federal and international copyright and other property laws. The compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement and assembly) of all content on this site is the exclusive property of Coupon Sense Inc. and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. All software used on this site is the property of Coupon Sense Inc., its partners or its software suppliers and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. The content and software on this site may be used as a consumer shopping resource. Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, re-publication, or display of the content on this site is strictly prohibited.

**Trademarks**

“Coupon Sense”, the CouponSense.com logo, “CouponSense.com”, “Best Clips of the Week”, “Best Clips”, “Clips of the Week”, and the taglines “Two bags for the price of one”, “Sensible Shopping Made Easy!” and “The Best Kept Secret in Arizona” are the service marks of Coupon Sense Inc. and may not be used without permission. All other product names contained in this website may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners.

**Miscellaneous**

No waiver of any breach of any provision of this Agreement shall constitute a waiver of any prior, concurrent or subsequent breach of the same or any other provisions hereof, and no waiver shall be effective unless made in writing and signed by an authorized representative of the waiving party. The Section headings used in this Agreement are intended for convenience only and shall not be deemed to supersede or modify any provisions.

**Coupon Sense Privacy Policy**

The following statement discloses consumer privacy practices for the website www.CouponSense.com and services portals associated with the online services offered to licensed users by CouponSense, Inc. (collectively, “Coupon Sense Websites”). Coupon Sense may update its policy from time to time without notice, so please check back periodically.

Privacy Policy updates will be published on the Coupon Sense website.

**Service Partners**

Through links on the Coupon Sense website and user services portals, you may interact with a number of Service Partners with whom Coupon Sense has a relationship to provide information and/or commercial e-mail services to its customers and end users. In general, personal information provided to Coupon Sense will be protected by such partners by requirements at least as strict as Coupon Sense’s own privacy policies. However, Coupon Sense is not responsible for the privacy practices of our Service Partners. As you visit their Websites and /or use their services, we encourage you to read their privacy statements, as they may differ from ours in some particulars.

**Personal Information**

Coupon Sense operates email services via the Coupon Sense Website for organizations ranging from small businesses to major enterprise customers and ISPs, Coupon Sense understands its customers’ need to protect personal and account information. In providing Coupon Sense and Coupon Sense Service Partner services to you, personal information may be gathered, tracked or used, to provide you with services and to suggest ways in which you can enhance the use of the Coupon Sense Websites.

In most cases, you will be asked to provide personal and account information for each service as appropriate for Coupon Sense to provide the service in a secure environment to you. This may include name, address, business, e-mail, US Mail, telephone, facsimile, or other information necessary to provide effective services, maintenance and support to your account and end users.

**Requested Information**

We request and use personal and customer information when you create an account, authorize end users, request or operate a Coupon Sense service, create and publish a data report, correspond with us or engage in other activities on our Websites. For example, if you request technical support online or via telephone, we will ask you for information necessary to authenticate you as a customer or end user, and to provide the requested support, such as your name, address and information about your computer hardware, software and the nature of the problem you are experiencing.

We also maintain logs to track usage of the Coupon Sense Websites by end users and to track maintenance and support dialogues with end users and customers. Providing such information is completely voluntary, and while individuals are under no obligation to provide such information to Coupon Sense, our customers may not get the full benefit of our products, services and support without providing such information.

**How We Use the Information We Gather and Track**

In many cases, you decide whether to authorize any activity that requests personal information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the activity. This includes operating Coupon Sense services online, as well as support and maintenance with you.

We use personal and account information in the following ways:

  * To provide you with information about the Coupon Sense Website, newsletters, informative emails, and alerts to future product ideas or improvements;
  * To assist us in providing end user support and account maintenance information;
  * To provide you access to Service Partner services and information that you have requested;
  * To assist us in creating better products and services to meet your future needs;
  * To provide you with access to services or otherwise engage in activities, such as protect testing or evaluation, that you select on the Coupon Sense Websites

**With Whom We May Share Your Information**

From time to time, unless we have stated otherwise, we may provide certain information to selected Service Partners in order to effectively provide the product or service requested. For example, in providing ISP mediation services for our customers, we may need to share information about the email campaign practices of your end users with support personnel at Internet abuse desks. Coupon Sense limits the provision of personally identifying information to a minimum in handling such matters, and does so only under a services agreement with your consent.

In addition, Coupon Sense may from time to time retain the services of outside contractors and Service Partners to provide and/or host online services for our customers. They may be used to provide online maintenance and technical support or perform other services for us. We require that these contractors keep the personal information of customers secure and confidential. We also require that these contractors and Service Partners use your personal and account information only on behalf of Coupon Sense and/or to suggest enhancements to your use of the Coupon Sense Websites.

If you prefer that we not provide your information to our Service Partners, you may let us know by using one of the methods described in this policy.

**Legal Disclosures**

Please be advised that in certain instances, it may be necessary for Coupon Sense to disclose your personal information to government officials or otherwise as required by our legal obligations. This could include a court proceeding that requires us to disclose such information.

**Limiting the Use of Personal Information**

Coupon Sense provides a number of ways for you to ‘opt-out’ of receiving additional information from us or having us provide your personal information to our Service Partners. We may offer you these choices at the time you give us your information and/or at the time you access Coupon Sense online service portals.

If you would like to change your user preferences and account information, you may contact Coupon Sense and/or access the administrative pages for your account on the applicable Coupon Sense Website.

If you do not wish to continue receiving any online promotional communications from Coupon Sense, such as e-mail or online newsletters, you can opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to the unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or changing your communication preferences on the administrative pages for your account.

**Security and Quality of Personal Information**

We have taken security measures to protect your personal information, including technical and procedural steps to protect your data from misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, loss, alteration or destruction.

Since Coupon Sense is a global company, we provide company information to our worldwide offices. The personal information that you have provided to us may be transferred to other Coupon Sense servers around the world. Also, in certain countries our outside contractors might undertake the collection, transferring, storage and processing of your information.

We make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to update or correct your personal information. If you believe that Coupon Sense does not have your current personal information, you can update it by using one of the communication channels at the bottom of this statement.

**Cookies**

Coupon Sense may use cookies from time to time. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individual’s computer that allows us to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in our databases. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. Coupon Sense may use cookies to personalize your experience on our online services or portal pages, or to track end user usage of Coupon Sense services for customers. If you do not want Coupon Sense to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a Website tries to put a cookie in your browser software. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use of some of the products and/or services at the Coupon Sense Websites.

Coupon Sense may also use cookies to track your visit to our Websites. While our Web servers may automatically log your IP address, such basic Internet traffic statistics will not be tied back to other personal information.

**Web Site Traffic**

We may track domain names, IP addresses, email addresses and browser types from people who visit our Websites. Such information is not correlated with any personal information.

**Other Privacy Management Practices**

Please remember that information you submit in a discussion group, blog or other forum will be deemed published, public information and is therefore no longer confidential. The communication of personal and account information in such venues means that that information can be collected and used by others, and you should assess that risk before doing so. This includes your disclosure of information concerning your account profile, personal data, or other data obtained by use of the Coupon Sense Websites.

**Policy Changes**

In the event there is a major change to Coupon Sense’ privacy practices, Coupon Sense will provide its users advance notice on the Coupon Sense website and/or user portal.

If the change involves the use of your personally identifiable information, the notice will contain instructions on how you can opt-out of such use or modify your information to suit the intended use.

If the change involves the use of your assigned user account information and/or related web and e-mail addresses, the notice will contain instructions on how you can access the administrative console on your portal to review and/or edit the information associated with your user account.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or comments, or if you would like to change your communication preferences, please contact us.

**CouponSense Inc.**  
sales@CouponSense.com  
partners@CouponSense.com  
support@CouponSense.com  
P.O. Box 193  
2040 S. Alma School Rd. Ste 1  
Chandler, AZ   
85286-0987  
480-883-9012

This Privacy notice is current as of September 20, 2010
